A long time ago, a powerful demon fox
appeared with nine tails.
With its powerful tails,
it could smash mountains
and create tidal waves.
A band of Shinobi rose to
defend their village from attack.
We have to wait until
the Fourth Hokage gets here!
We can't let it get any closer
to our village!
One great Shinobi was able to
imprison the monster,
but died in the process.
This Shinobi was known as...
the Fourth Hokage.
Naruto!
Why did you do such a thing?!
You're really gonna get it this time!
I don't care!
You know your problem?
You can't do the things I do!
Only I can do this!
I'm better than all of you!
There's a problem, sir!
Hokage-sama!
What is it?
Did that Naruto do something again?
Yes. He climbed onto
the Mountainside Images...
And he vandalized and
graffitied all over them!
Wait!
Ha ha...
Why should I?
Hey, Naruto!
How did you suddenly get here,
Iruka-sensei?
The question is what are you doing here
when you should be in class now?
Now listen, Naruto.
You failed the last graduation test
and the one before that.
This is no time
to be goofing off, you fool!
We will have a re-test on
the Transformation Jutsu!
Even those who already passed
will take it!
What?!
Haruno Sakura. Here I go...
Transform!
Okay!
I did it!
Shannaro!
Did you see that, Sasuke-kun?
Next, Uchiha Sasuke.
Yes.
O-Okay.
Next, Uzumaki Naruto.
This is a real pain.
And it's all your fault.
Like I care!!
Okay...
Good luck, Naruto-kun...
Transform!
How was it?
I call it the "Sexy Jutsu"!
You fool!
Stop making idiotic spells!
Damn...
I won't let you go home
unless you clean that all up.
I don't care...
There's nobody home anyway.
Naruto...
What is it this time?
What I meant was...
If you clean up all that mess,
I'll buy you ramen tonight.
Huh?!
Yes!
I-I will finish it no time!
Enter!
Uzumaki Naruto
Naruto.
Why did you vandalize those faces?
Don't you know who
the Hokage leaders are?
Of course, I do!
I know they earned the
title of Hokage
because they were the best Ninja
of their time, right?
Especially the Fourth Hokage
was a hero
who saved the village from
the nine-tail demon fox.
Then why did you do that?
Because I'll become a Hokage myself.
And I'll be the greatest Hokage
of all time!
So that everyone will finally
learn to accept me!
By the way, Sensei,
I have a favor to ask.
You want another bowl?
Mmmm... No...
Can I borrow that Leaf headband
for a while?
This?
No no!
This is worn only by those who
have graduated from Ninja Academy.
Tomorrow, you will...
You're so mean!
So that's why you took off
your goggles...
Humph...
One more bowl please!
We are now about to begin
the graduation test.
When your name is called,
proceed to the next classroom.
The test is on the Clone Jutsu.
Oh no...
Of all the...! That is my weakest Jutsu!
But still...
I will do it no matter what!
Clone Jutsu!
Disqualified!
Iruka-sensei.
His physical coordination
and stamina are excellent.
And he managed to come up
with something.
Isn't that enough
for him to pass?
Mizuki-sensei...
All the others created three or more clones.
Naruto created just one.
And it's practically useless.
I can't give him a passing mark.
I'm a Ninja now!
You did well. That's my son.
Congratulations for your graduation.
I'll cook something good tonight!
Look at that one.
It's that boy.
I hear he's the only one who failed.
Serves him right.
Imagine what would happen
if he became a Shinobi.
Isn't that the boy
who is actually...
Hey! We're not supposed to
talk about that.
Iruka.
We need to talk later.
Yes, sir.
Iruka-sensei isn't trying
to be mean to you.
Then why only me?
He wants you to become strong
from the bottom of his heart.
You both don't have parents.
But I really wanted to graduate.
Heh... I guess I have no choice...
I'll let you in on a big secret.
Secret?
Iruka.
What is it, Hokage-sama?
I know how you feel. But...
Naruto also grew up without knowing
the love of his parents... like you.
Let me go!
My mom and dad are
still out there fighting!
Wake up, Iruka-sensei!
What's the matter?
Come to Hokage-sama's immediately!
I heard that Naruto-kun...
stole the Scroll of Sealing.
The Scroll of Sealing?!
Let's see...
The first Jutsu is...
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu?
What?! Already a Jutsu I'm no good at?
Hokage-sama!
We can't forgive him!
This is not just a prank!
The Scroll is a dangerous item
that the First Hokage sealed!
Depending on its use...
It will be a major disaster if
it is taken out of the village!
Yes. Bring Naruto here at once!
Yes, sir!
Where did you go... Naruto?
I will tell everyone in the village
about this and eliminate Naruto...
Then the Scroll of Sealing
will be mine!
Hey you, Naruto!
You found me..
And I've only learned one Jutsu.
He's been practicing the Jutsu...
until he's become
this exhausted and dirty...?
Listen, listen!
I'm gonna show you this amazing Jutsu!
You're gonna let me graduate
if I can do it!
Isn't it true that I can graduate if
I can do one of the Jutsu written here?
Who told you that?
Mizuki-sensei. He told me
about this scroll, and this place...
Mizuki did?!
I'm impressed you found this place.
I see now... how it is.
Naruto, give me that scroll.
Wait, wait...
What's going on here?
Naruto! Never give him that scroll!
It is a dangerous object that contains
forbidden Ninja Jutsu. It was sealed.
Mizuki used you in order to
get it for himself!
W-Wha...?
Naruto, Iruka is only afraid of
you holding that scroll!
Huh?
What are you saying, Mizuki!
Don't let him fool you, Naruto!
I will tell you the truth.
Idiot! Don't do that!
After an incident 12 years ago,
a rule was created.
A rule?
That is, Naruto, a rule everybody
but you knows.
Except me?!
What is it?
Stop it, Mizuki!
The rule forbids anyone from revealing
that you are actually the Demon Fox Spirit!
Huh?
You are actually the Demon,
Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit,
who killed Iruka's parents and
destroyed our village!
Stop it!
Everyone has been
deceiving you ever since.
Didn't you find it strange?
Why everyone hated you so much?
No! No! No! No! No!
Naruto...
Nobody accepts you.
That's why Iruka hates you so much!
Iruka... Naruto grew up
without the love of parents.
Everyone avoids him like
the plague after what happened.
That's why he keeps misbehaving.
It's the only way for him to get
any attention or acknowledgment.
He pretends to be tough,
but inside he is really hurting.
Die, Naruto!
Naruto!
Get down!
Why...?
Because you and I are the same.
After my parents died,
nobody paid attention to me
or gave me any support.
I wasn't a good student in school.
I was the class clown...
because I wanted people to notice me.
I couldn't get noticed through excellence,
so I kept doing stupid things.
It was so hard.
Isn't that right, Naruto?
You felt so lonely... right?
And you suffered inside, right?
I'm sorry, Naruto...
If I had been more responsible,
maybe you wouldn't have suffered so much.
Don't make me laugh!
Iruka has always hated you,
ever since you killed his parents!
He's just saying all that
to get the Scroll of Sealing back!
Naruto!
He is not the type of kid
who will change his mind.
He will take revenge against
our village using that scroll!
Didn't you see his eyes?
Those are the eyes of a Demon Fox.
No...
Naruto... isn't... like that at all!
All I want is to kill Naruto
and get the scroll.
I'll take care of you later!
I-I won't let you...
Well, well.
Mizuki has a big mouth!
Naruto feels worse than he's ever felt.
He might unleash
the power locked up inside him.
The Scroll of Sealing is now with him.
There's a slight chance
he might actually release
the Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit
sealed inside him!
If that happens...
I've found him!
Naruto!
Everything that Mizuki said
was a lie!
Give me that scroll, quick!
Mizuki is after the scroll!
It can't be...
Why is it, Naruto?
How...
did you know I wasn't Iruka...?
Because I'm Iruka.
I see.
What's in it for you to protect
the one who killed your family?
I'm not gonna let a stupid idiot
like you get that scroll!
You're the idiot.
Naruto is the same as me.
Same?
Anyone can do whatever
he wants once he has the scroll.
There is no way that that monster...
that Fox Spirit, won't take advantage
of the power of that scroll!
You're right...
I guess it was true all along!
See, Iruka-sensei never really
cared for me at all!
... if he was the Demon Fox Spirit.
But Naruto is different!
I know that he is an exceptional student.
He works very hard,
and he's single-minded
and clumsy at the same time.
No one accepts him, but he knows
the meaning of human suffering.
He is not the Demon Fox Spirit.
He's Uzumaki Naruto of
the Village Hidden in the Leaves!
You are so gullible.
Iruka!
I was gonna take you down later,
but I have changed my mind.
Die!
I guess this is the end for me...
Naruto?!
You surprised me there, freak.
If you ever lay a hand on Iruka-sensei,
I'll kill you!
Shut up! I can take care of a kid
like you with a single blow!
Why don't you try then?
I'll strike you back a thousand-fold!
Let's see you try!
Show me what you can do, Demon Fox!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Naruto! You've...
Those aren't just images but actual clones!
That's an advanced Ninjutsu!
What's this...?
What's the matter?
C'mon!
Weren't you gonna get me
with one blow? Here!
In that case...
I'll come to you.
I kinda got carried away.
Iruka-sensei, are you okay?
Yeah.
He's really something.
Maybe it is true.
Maybe he will surpass all
the Hokage leaders...
Naruto, come over here.
I'd like to give you something.
Has anyone found Naruto yet?
No.
Damn, this is going to be bad...
There's no need to worry anymore.
Hokage-sama!
He'll be back soon.
Sensei, how much longer?
Okay, you may open your eyes now.
Congratulations... on your graduation.
In celebration, we'll have ramen tonight!
Iruka-sensei!
That hurts!
Naruto...
I was going to lecture to you...
that the road gets more difficult
now that you're a Shinobi.
But I guess I'll just wait to tell you
that until we get to the ramen stand...
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
W-What do you want, you little shrimp?
Quit following me!
You're smaller than me and
you're saying that you're gonna
become the Fifth Hokage?
I don't care if you are the Third Hokage's
grandson or not.
It's not that easy to be a Hokage!
If you want it that bad,
you're gonna have to beat me first!
Next episode:
"I am Konohamaru!"
Watch my outstanding performance!